SARBESH KUMAR TIWARI

B.TECH COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING (DATA SCIENCE & ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE)



8708828835



sarbeshtiwari39@gmail.com



Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

About Me

Highly motivated and skilled software engineer with experience in developing and maintaining software applications. Participated in different Hackathons. Proficient in multiple programming languages Java, Python, Dart and C, including markup languages HTML and CSS and experienced in working with Agile development methodologies. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to work well in a team environment.

Experience

Chegg 02/2022 - Present

Subject Matter Expert

 Addressed a diverse range of issues within the realm of Computer Science, effectively finding and implementing solutions.

Chegg 01/2023 - Present

Textbook solution Expert

• Helping students to deepen their understanding by providing solutions to textbook problems.

Education

B.tech Computer Science Engineering

Shri Ramswaroop Memorial University, Barabanki Uttar Peadesh

2020-2024

XII

Kendriya Vidyalaya Lucknow Cantt, Lucknow

2020

Χ

Kendriya Vidyalaya Lucknow Cantt, Lucknow

2018

Language

Python

Java

C

Dart

_ -----

HTML CSS

Skills

- Programming languages:
 Java, Python, C
- Frameworks: Flutter
- Databases: MySQL
- Agile development methodologies
- Strong problem-solving skills

Certificates

- Smart India Hackathon 2022
- ML in Python,
- ML in sound with Python
- Data analysis using Python
- Data Science in Python
- Enterprise design thinking
- Hadoop Fundamentals